panasianbiz.com 2007-06-08

# PanAsianBiz: Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy of KnowMoreMedia

This policy covers user privacy, system security, and KnowMoreMedia information collection practices. This Privacy Policy Statement applies only to KnowMoreMedia web sites. You are encouraged to check Privacy Policies when going to another web site. 

These World Wide Web pages are provided as a service by KnowMoreMedia

Information presented on these pages is considered copywrited information and may not be distributed or copied without express written consent. 

Site Management Data:

KnowMoreMedia Web servers automatically collect information for site management and for statistical purposes. This computer system uses software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. 

The use of "cookies":

KnowMoreMedia may assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

Third Party Cookies  
Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This may be done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. KnowMoreMedia does not have access to this data.

Consent to Voluntary Information Collection and Sharing:

All the information users submit to KnowMoreMedia is done on a voluntary basis. When a user clicks the "Submit" button on any of the Web forms found on KnowMoreMedia's sites they are indicating voluntarily consent to the conditions outlined in this policy. We do not collect personally identifiable information (e.g., name, address, phone number, e-mail address) unless you provide it. In all cases, the information collected is used to respond to user inquiries or to provide services requested by our users.

How e-mail is handled:

We use information you send us by e-mail only for the purpose for which it is submitted (e.g., to answer a question, to send information). In addition, if you do choose to provide information, it is only used to respond to your request (e.g., addressing a package to send you pamphlets or booklets) or to provide a service you are requesting (e.g., email notifications). 

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don't currently send advertising via email, but in the future that may change and our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you want to remove your email address please contact us via our contact form.

Comments/Message Boards

The majority of KnowMoreMedia websites contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce "comment spam." These email addresses will not be shared with any third party. While your email address will not be shared with any third party, the actual body and content of the comments and messages you submit are considered public property, and are published on the blog. So please don't offer any personal information in the body or content of your comments, unless you want that information displayed to the online world. We will actively remove "comment spam" from our comment sections.

How information is used:

The information KnowMoreMedia collects is used for a variety of purposes. We make every effort to clearly disclose at the point of collection how information is used and allow our Web site visitor to determine whether they wish to provide the information.

How long information is retained:

We periodical destroy the information we collect when the purpose for which it was provided has been fulfilled.

Ownership of Information  
KnowMoreMedia is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites. However, if KnowMoreMedia is acquired by another firm, they may gain ownership of this information.

Links  
KnowMoreMedia websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by KnowMoreMedia.

Interaction with Children:

KnowMoreMedia offers educational content to site visitors that may include children under 13. No personally identifiable information is collected from these visitors unless voluntarily submitted as a request for information or services. The information collected is used to respond to user inquiries or to provide services requested by our users. 

Privacy Act System of Records:

KnowMoreMedia does not maintain and retrieve information submitted to it based upon personal identifiers (name, email addresses, etc.). Consequently, KnowMoreMedia Web sites do not use or collect information for any Privacy Act System of Records.

Traffic Reports  
Our traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers as well as trying to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

Information Protection:

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to the information on our Web sites. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited.

Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits

Your Rights Under the Privacy Act:

Privacy Act Reference Materials. 

Dispute Resolution:

If for some reason you believe this site has not adhered to these principles, please notify KnowMoreMedia, Inc by the e-mail listed on our contact page. If our web pages are not fully in compliance with our stated policies, they will be corrected.
